GORAN RADMANOVIC

Web Developer

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

I'm a web developer, who likes new technologies, challenges and new experience and I'm a guick learner. You can easily find me and contact me through social accounts or on email address. It would be a great honor to work with you.

WORK EXPERIENCE

FRONT END DEVELOPER, FREELANCE

MAY 2023 - Present

FRONT END DEVELOPER, DIGIMONDO

MAY 2021 - MAY 2023

I was working remotely as frontend developer on the enterprise web application for IoT industry. The Internet of Things is already fundamentally changing our world and our lives.

FRONT END DEVELOPER, EXAMIZ DEC 2020 - AVG 2021

WEB DEVELOPER, WEBIMPACTO JUN 2020 - JUN 2021

WEB DEVELOPER, OOMOVERS JUL 2019 - JUL 2021

OTHER EXPERIENCE

https://goranradmanovic.github.io/#experience

PROJECTS

https://goranradmanovic.github.io/#projects

SKILLS

- JavaScript
- VueJS
- NuxtJS
- PHP & MySQL
- HTML & CSS
- SASS
- GIT
- **PWA**
- SPA
- Laravel
- Veutify
- **Bootstrap**
- **TailwindCSS**
- NodeJS
- Firebase



CONTACT

goranradmanovic@gmail.com

https://goranradmanovic.github.io/

https://www.linkedin.com/in/goranradmanovic-70814a9b/

ACADEMIC BACKGROUND

Faculty of Sciences, BSc University in Banja Luka

COURSES

- Basic Course Of Javascript, ICBL
- Basic Course Of PHP & MySQL, ICBL
- Basic Course Of Java, ICBL
- OOP Course In PHP, INFOARS
- Advanced Course In PHP, INFOARS
- Beginning Course In PHP, INFOARS
- WordPress Course, ICBL
- Team Work Course, ICBL

LANGUAGES

- Serbian / Bosnian / Croatian
- English (C2)

HOBBIES

- Running
- Cycling
- **Blood donor**